Dam Uyen Ha

ACCOUNTANT

L +84909717398 ■ damuyenha@gmail.com • Ho Chi Minh , Viet Nam

SUMMARY

Hà is a detail-oriented with a passion for numbers. With over 2 years of experience in accounts receivable and internal accounting within the manufacturing sector, she has meticulous attention to detail and is a careful approach to her work. She is eager to learn and stay updated on new information and is known for being a cheerful and supportive team player

WORK EXPERIENCE

SANYO MINH LONG CO.,

07/2022 - Now

Accountant/Account Receivable

- Conducted monthly bank reconciliations, ensuring accurate financial records. Handled customer inquiries related to billing, invoices, and payment options, resolving issues promptly.
- Managed accounts receivable, contacting clients via phone, email, and mail to ensure timely collections.
- Reconciled account balances and updated revenue/expense records using Misa accounting software.
- Monitored daily bank deposits and updated accounting systems accordingly.
- Oversaw internal advance settlement on a weekly and monthly basis.
- Processed supplier payments on a weekly schedule.
- Assisted with additional tasks as assigned by the manager.

HONG HA LOGISTICS 08/2021 - 05/2022

Internal Accountant

- Managed and monitored accounts receivable by contacting clients via phone, email, and mail, ensuring timely collections and maintaining
 accurate records.
- Maintained and updated employee compensation and benefits data, ensuring precision in salary, bonuses, and benefits using Micosoft Office system.
- Collaborated with pricing and accounting teams to ensure accurate financial reporting and alignment with company goals.

EDUCATION

HUFLIT UNIVERSITY

2016 - 2021

Bachelor Degree

CERTIFICATIONS

TOEIC - 860pt

GENERAL ACOUNTING PRACTICE COURSE

SKILLS

Soft skills:

- · Mathematical Reasoning
- · Problem-solving

- Communication
- Team work
- Independent work
- Attention to detail
- Ethical judgment

Hard skills:

- Accounting software (Misa)
- Microsoft Office
- Google Workspace

INTERESTS

Picnic, travel and sport